Dad.
The house has been sealed.
You'll have to make do for now.
Jinwen.
Although I've caught the drug smuggler,
the mastermind is still at large.
If your spirits are watching from above,
please help me find the real culprit.
This roll of film came in a strange way.
It's not evidence.
I can only ask for your help.
German-made.
This is Leica's new 35mm film.
It's very expensive,
so it's extremely rare in the country.
What exactly is in here?
Want to know?
Don't worry.
I'll handle it for you.
Come find me tomorrow.
Ningning.
What did Bai Xianming say before he died?
He only said the word "hospital".
Hospital?
I think Bai Xianming just wanted
to be rushed to the hospital.
Not necessarily.
He probably meant
St. George's Hospital in the British Concession.
Our last visit to St. George's Hospital
might have alerted them.
How should we proceed with the case?
Superintendent Li,
we've known each other for seven years.
When I first came to Phoenix Police Academy,
you were the one who showed me the ropes.
I've always seen you as my senior.
Just say what you want to say.
Don't beat around the bush.
I remember you used to be a good cop.
While apprehending suspects,
you stayed on the front lines even after being shot.
What exactly are you trying to say?
As far as I know,
this banned drug smuggling case
is being watched by many big shots above.
It has some connection to the suburban bone pile case.
If you turn back now,
it's still not too late.
Jiang Siyao, what do you mean?
You're an excellent detective,
and I'm the corrupt cop?
What are you doing?
Police.
Have you seen the girl in the photo?
No.
You've seen this girl,
haven't you?
I said I haven't seen her.
Let's check somewhere else.
Can't you speak nicely?
Let's go, Ningning.
The church symbol behind the girl in the photo
is exactly the same as the one here.
This Lei Lie is really a wolf in sheep's clothing.
Jiang Siyao.
I'm telling you,
either you kill me,
or you let me go.
Stop wasting time.
I traveled all over when I was young.
I've seen it all.
Bring it on if you have the guts.
If I make a sound,
I'll take your last name.
Lei Lie,
you probably don't know yet.
This case is now
personally supervised by the central special envoy.
The person behind you not only can't protect you,
but actually hopes you won't say a word.
You'd better think carefully
about how they can guarantee you won't say a word.
Do you think
you have much time left to live?
Have you seen this photo?
This person.
Never seen him.
I'll give you one last chance.
Are you going to talk
or not?
Ye Shian, are you crazy?
Do you know you're still injured?
Why did you call us here?
I'm all better.
If I don't catch this bad guy,
and find out what happened to my brothers,
I won't have a day of peace.
Besides,
I found out that the girl in the photo,
who was assaulted,
worked here half a year ago
and then suddenly quit.
I suspect it has something to do with that incident.
Maybe we can find some clues here.
I wonder which gentleman is looking for me.
Boss, I want to ask you about someone.
Do you know this person?
Why are you looking for her?
What happened to her?
This girl
is a jinx.
Since she came, my business has been bad.
She either slacked off or served the wrong dishes.
She was always distracted.
By the way,
every time she saw foreigners coming to eat,
she would scream like she was possessed
and hide.
I think
she just wanted to slack off
and didn't want to work.
So I sent her away.
Could it be that the people here bullied her?
What do you mean by that, miss?
I see you three are not here to eat,
but to pick a fight.
You didn't even ask around where this is.
This is Zuixian Restaurant,
my territory.
Men!
This Zuixian Restaurant is really a shady inn.
Kick them out!
You!
If you move again, don't blame me for being ruthless.
Be careful with your wound next time.
It's fine. I'm all better.
Why did you come to the missionary hospital?
Where do I pay, doctor?
Go out and turn right.
Please take a seat.
Hello, Dr. Peter.
What's bothering you?
I've been having migraines lately.
Can you prescribe some medicine for me?
Of course.
I'll prescribe some medicine for you
to make you feel better.
Doctor,
do you like photography very much?
Yes.
I really like the scenery in China.
Looking at these photos of yours,
they are all so beautiful.
What kind of camera did you use?
Well,
it's not about the camera,
but the film.
I used the latest
Leica 35mm film produced in Germany.
I
brought it all the way from abroad.
Is it beautiful?
Beautiful.
Not as beautiful as you.
Thank you.
How is it?
Look inside.
Could it be him?
I'm sure
the photo of the abused girl
was taken by Pete.
What are we waiting for? Let's arrest him.
Arrest him.
Wait.
Are you crazy?
This is a hospital in the Concession.
We'll come back tonight.
Okay, let's go.
I'll go back to get some clean clothes.
See you at the church entrance later.
Okay.
I'll go in first, and you cover me from outside.
I'd better go with you.
No.
If anything happens, we can look out for each other.
Don't worry.
I have a surprise for you.
So beautiful.
Please let me go.
No!